Guide to the Student Volunteer Movement for Foreign Missions Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Relationships with Other Organizations, Series IX
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Committee of Reference and Counsel (Box 644, Folder 7389)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Commission on Missions in a New Age (Box 644, Folder 7390)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Committee on Missionary Personnel (Box 644, Folder 7391-7394)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Committee on Missionary Personnel (Box 645, Folder 7395)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Committee on World Literary and Christian Literature (Box 645, Folder 7396)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Committee to Study the Christian Approach to Communism (Box 645, Folder 7397)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Joint Committee on Foreign Students (Box 645, Folder 7398)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America -- misc. (Box 645, Folder 7399)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Regional Meetings, 1948 (Box 645, Folder 7400,7401)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Resettlement committee (Box 645, Folder 7402)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America - Rural Missions Cooperating Committee (Box 645, Folder 7403)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America Seminar in Ecumenics and Missions (Box 645, Folder 7404)
  - Foreign Missions Conference of North America World Mission Assembly 1948 (Box 645, Folder 7405)
  - Free Methodist Church of North America (Box 645, Folder 7406)
  - Friands Foreign Missionary Society of Ohio Yearly Meeting (Box 645, Folder 7407)
  - General Conference Mennonite Church (Box 645, Folder 7408)
  - General Conference of Seventh Day Adventists (Box 645, Folder 7409)
  - General Council of the Evangelical Lutheran Church in North America (Box 645, Folder 7410)
  - General Synod of the Evangelical Lutheran Church in the U.S.A. (Box 645, Folder 7411)
  - Home Missions Council of North America (Box 646, Folder 7412-7415)
  - Inter-church Student Conference (Box 646, Folder 7416)
  - International Church of the Foursquare Gospel (Box 646, Folder 7417)
  - International Council of Religious Education (Box 646, Folder 7418)
  - International Grenfell Association 7420-7422 International Missionary Council: Madras conference (Box 646, Folder 7419)
  - International Missionary Council: Madras conference (Box 647, Folder 7423-7427)
  - International Missionary Council: post-Madras conferences (Box 647, Folder 7428,7429)
  - International Missionary Council: miscellaneous (Box 647, Folder 7430)
  - International Student Service (See also: World Student Service Fund) (Box 647, Folder 7431)
  - International Voluntary Services, Inc. (Box 647, Folder 7432)
  - International Voluntary Services, Inc. (Box 648, Folder 7433,7434)
  - Interseminary Movement (Box 648, Folder 7435-7437)
  - Intervarsity Christian Fellowship (Box 648, Folder 7438-7440)
  - Japan International Christian University (Box 648, Folder 7441)
  - Japanese Students Christian Association in North America (Box 648, Folder 7442)
  - Joint Committee on United Youth Program (Box 648, Folder 7443)
  - Koinonia Foundation (Box 648, Folder 7444)
  - Latin America Evangelization Campaign (Box 648, Folder 7445)
  - Laymen's Missionary Movement (Box 648, Folder 7446,7447)
  - Lisle Fellowship (Box 649, Folder 7448,7449)
  - Lott Carey Baptist Foreign Missions Convention (Box 649, Folder 7450)
  - Lutheran Free Church (Box 649, Folder 7451)
  - Lutheran Orient Mission (Box 649, Folder 7452)
  - Lutheran Student Association of Amerlca (Box 649, Folder 7453)
  - Mennonite Board of Mission and Charities (Box 649, Folder 745L)
  - Mennonite Church of North America (Box 649, Folder 7455)
  - Methodist Church (Box 649, Folder 7456-7460)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 649, Folder 7461-7464)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 650, Folder 7465)
  - Methodist Episcopal Church South (Box 650, Folder 7566)
  - Methodist Protestant Church (Box 650, Folder 7467)
  - Metropolitan Church Association (Box 650, Folder 7468)
  - Mission Covenant Church (Box 650, Folder 7469)
  - Missionary Education Movement of the U.S. and Canada (Box 650, Folder 7470-7476)
  - Missionary Research Library (Box 650, Folder 7477,7478)
  - The Missionary Review of the World (Box 651, Folder 7479)
  - A Movement for World Christianity (Box 651, Folder 7480)
  - National Assembly of Student Christian Associations (Box 651, Folder 7481-7487)
  - National Baptist Convention (Box 651, Folder 7488)
  - National Cooperating Committee on Christian Reconstruction (Box 651, Folder 7489,7490)
  - National Cooperating Committee on Christian Re construct ion (Box 652, Folder 7491-7500)
  - National Cooperating Committee on Christian Reconstruction (Box 653, Folder 7501)
  - National Council of Churches of Christ in America: Administrative staff matters (Box 653, Folder 7502-7504)
  - NCCCUSA Commission on Chritian Higher Education (Box 653, Folder 7505, 7506)
  - NCCCUSA Commission on Missionary Education (Box 653, Folder 7507)
  - NCCCUSA Constituting Convention (Box 653, Folder 7508)
  - NCCCUSA Department of Campus Christian Life (Box 653, Folder 7509,7510)
  - NCCCUSA Department of Campus Christian Life (Box 654, Folder 7511-7513)
  - NCCCUSA Department of International Affairs (Box 654, Folder 7514)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Christian Life and Work (Box 654, Folder 7515)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Foreign Missions: Annual Assemblies,1952-1954 (Box 654, Folder 7516-7518)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Foreign Missions: Committee on Missionary Personnel (Box 654, Folder 7519-7521)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Foreign Missions: Executive Board (Box 655, Folder 7522-7525)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Foreign Missions: Missionary Obligation of the Church (Box 655, Folder 7526)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Foreign Missions: Staff Council (Box 655, Folder 7527)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Foreign Missions: Technical Assistance Program (Box 655, Folder 7528)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Foreign Missions: Miscellaneous communications (Box 655, Folder 7529)
  - NCCCUSA Division of Home Missions: Annual Assemblies (Box 655, Folder 7530)
  - NCC WSA Division of Home Missions: Ecumenical work camps (Box 655, Folder 7531)
  - NCCCUSA Executive Staff (Box 655, Folder 7532)
  - NCCCUSA General Board (Box 656, Folder 7533)
  - NCCCUSA Joint Commission on Missionary Education (Box 656, Folder 7534-7538)
  - NCCCUSA Joint Department of American Communities Overseas (Box 656, Folder 7539)
  - NCCCUSA Joint Department of Ghristian Vocation (Box 656, Folder 7540)
  - NCCCUSA Silver Bay Conference on the Christian World Mission (Box 657, Folder 7541)
  - NCCCUSA World Literacy and Christian Literature (Box 657, Folder 7542)
  - National Council of Student Christian Associations (Box 657, Folder 7543,7544)
  - National Holiness Missionary Society (Box 657, Folder 7545)
  - National Intercollegiate Christian Council (Box 657, Folder 7546)
  - NICC, 1940 (Box 657, Folder 7547-7551)
  - NICC, 1941 (Box 657, Folder 7552-7556)
  - NICC, 1942 (Box 658, Folder 7557-7560)
  - NICC, 1943 (Box 658, Folder 7561,7562)
  - NICC, 1944 (Box 658, Folder 7563)
  - NICC, 1945 (Box 658, Folder 7564)
  - NICC, 1946 (Box 658, Folder 7565)
  - NICC, 1947 (Box 658, Folder 7566)
  - NICC, 1948 (Box 659, Folder 7567,7568)
  - NICC, 1949, 1950 (Box 659, Folder 7569)
  - NICC, 1951 (Box 659, Folder 7570)
  - National Lutheran Council (Box 659, Folder 7571)
  - National Student Christian Federation (Box 659, Folder 7572)
  - National Student Council of the YMCA and YWCA 1952-1954 (Box 659, Folder 7573-7578)
  - National Student Council of the YMCA and YWCA 1955, 1956 (Box 660, Folder 7579-7580)
  - The Navigators (Box 660, Folder 7582)
  - Near East College Association (Box 660, Folder 7583)
  - New Zealand Student Christian Movement (Box 660, Folder 7584)
  - North American Baptist General Missionary Society, Inc. (Box 660, Folder 7585)
  - North American Ecumenical Conference (Box 660, Folder 7586)
  - Northern Baptist Convention (Box 660, Folder 7587,7588)
  - Norwegian Lutheran Church of America (Box 660, Folder 7589)
  - Ohio Commission on Students and the World Christian Community (Box 660, Folder 7590)
  - Orthodox Presbyterian Church (Box 660, Folder 7591)
  - Pilgrim Fellowship (Box 660, Folder 7592)
  - Presbyterian Church in Canada (Box 660, Folder 7593)
  - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America (Box 660, Folder 7594-7597)
  - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America (Box 660, Folder 7598,7599)
  - Presbyterian Church in the United States of America (Box 661, Folder 7600-7605)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church (Box 661, Folder 7606,7607)
  - Reformed Church in America (Box 661, Folder 7608)
  - Reformed Church in the United States (Box 661, Folder 7609)
  - Reformed Presbyterian Church in North America (Box 661, Folder 7610)
  - Religious Society of Friends of Philadelphia and Vicinity (Box 661, Folder 7611)
  - Rural Missions Cooperative Committee (Box 661, Folder 7612)
  - Salvation Army (Box 661, Folder 7613)
  - Santal Mission of the Northern Churches (Box 661, Folder 7614)
  - Seventh Day Baptist Missionary Society (Box 661, Folder 7615)
  - Southern Baptist Convention (Box 661, Folder 7616,7617)
  - Student Christian Movement in New England (Box 661, Folder 7618,7619)
  - Student Christian Movement in New England (Box 662, Folder 7620-7628)
  - Student Christian Movement in New England re. Froncon,1947 (Box 662, Folder 7629,7630)
  - Student Christian Movement in New England re. SVM retreat, 1947 (Box 662, Folder 7631,7632)
  - Student Christian Movement in New York State (Box 663, Folder 7633)
  - Student Christian Movement of Canada (Box 663, Folder 7635-7636)
  - Student Christian Movement of Great Britain and Ireland (Box 663, Folder 7637,7638)
  - Student Christian Movement of India, Burma, and Ceylon (Box 663, Folder 7639)
  - Student Christian Movement of the Middle Atlantic Region (Box 663, Folder 7640-7642)
  - Student Christian Movement of the Southwest (Box 663, Folder 7644)
  - Student Fellowship for Christian Life-Service (Box 663, Folder 7645)
  - Student Volunteer Movement for the Near East (Box 663, Folder 7646)
  - The Unevangelized Tribes Mission (Box 663, Folder 7647)
  - Unitarian Service Committee (Box 663, Folder 7648)
  - United Baptist Convention of the Maritime Provinces (Box 663, Folder 7649)
  - United Board for Christian Colleges in China (Box 663, Folder 7650)
  - United Brethren in Christ (Box 663, Folder 7651)
  - United Christian Missionary Society (Box 663, Folder 7652)
  - United Christian Missionary Society (Box 664, Folder 7654,7655)
  - United Christian Youth Movement (Box 664, Folder 7656-7660)
  - United Church of Canada (Box 664, Folder 7661)
  - United Lutheran Church in America (Box 664, Folder 7662)
  - United Presbyterian Church of North America (Box 664, Folder 7663)
  - United States Conference for the World Council of Churches (Box 664, Folder 7664)
  - United Student Christian Council 1948 (Box 664, Folder 7665,7666)
  - United Student Christian Council 1948-1953 (Box 665, Folder 7667-7675)
  - United Student Christian Council 1953-1958 (Box 666, Folder 7676-7684)
  - United Student Peace Committee (Box 666, Folder 7685)
  - University Christian Mission (Box 667, Folder 7686-7692)
  - Vellore Christian Medical College Board (Box 667, Folder 7693)
  - Woman's Union Missionary Society of America (Box 667, Folder 7694)
  - Women's Christian College, Madras (Box 667, Folder 7695)
  - World Conference of Christian Youth (Box 667, Folder 7696)
  - World Council of Christian Education (Box 667, Folder 7697)
  - World Council of Churches (Box 667, Folder 7698)
  - World's Student Christian Federation (Box 667, Folder 7699)
  - World's Student Christian Federation (Box 668, Folder 7700-7705)
  - World Student Service Fund (See also: International Student Service and World University Service) (Box 668, Folder 7706)
  - World University Service (Box 668, Folder 7707,7708)
  - World University Service (Box 669, Folder 7709-7711)
  - World's Sunday School Association (Box 669, Folder 7712)
  - Yale-in-China (Box 669, Folder 7713)
  - Yenching College for Women (Box 669, Folder 7714)
  - Young Men's Christian Associations (misc.) (Box 669, Folder 7715)
  - YMCA - YWCA (Box 669, Folder 7716,7717)
  - Young Women's Christian Associations (Box 669, Folder 7718,7719)
  - Young Women's Christian Associations: Missionary Institute at Lake Geneva 1894 (Box 669, Folder 7720)
- Photographs, Series X
  The photographs in this Series were primarily used for publicity purposes. They include:
  A. Portraits of individuals, including SVM officers, traveling secretaries and student volunteers
  B. Group portraits from SVM conferences or union meetings, mostly unidentified
  C. Photographs portraying missionary activity overseas and in the United States.
  - Individuals
    - A-Sh (Box 670, Folder 7721-7739)
    - Si-Z (Box 671, Folder 7740-7744)
  - Student Volunteer Conferences and Groups
    - Student Volunteer Conferences and Groups (mostly unidentified) (Box 671, Folder 7745-7748)
  - Scenes of Missionary Activity
    - Africa (Box 671, Folder 7749)
    - Burma (Box 671, Folder 7750)
    - China (Box 671, Folder 7751)
    - India (Box 671, Folder 7752)
    - Japan (Box 671, Folder 7753)
    - Korea (Box 671, Folder 7754)
    - Middle East (Box 671, Folder 7755)
    - Philippines (Box 671, Folder 7756)
    - South America and the Caribbean (Box 671, Folder 7757)
    - U.S.A. (Box 671, Folder 7758)
    - Unidentified (Box 671, Folder 7759)